So you're suggesting that it was OK for slaves bodies to not only be used for labor, but also used to empower those who are harming them to be to be fairly represented in government?
I think it's absolutely they should have been used, period.
OK, so then we agree on that. So we agree on that.
It was absolutely abhorrent. There is no excuse for it. There's no justification for it.
Where's the argument? Because ultimately, when there was an opportunity in Reconstruction for there to be equality and humans considered in a real way and protected.
Democrats torched it. Andrew Johnson.
Yes, as well as the Supreme Court. That's actually more important.
What we need we have to acknowledge the Supreme Court torched it.
The Supreme Court has actively throughout this entire existence of this nation been at the forefront of impeding any advancement.
And it ends up sending us back over and over and over again because it doesn't have term limits because it is it doesn't have term limits.
You know, it's not it's not elected. It's appointed.
And ultimately, they have made it abundantly clear that they pick and choose when it's the states that are going to have rights and when they're going to be in a federal position of precedent.
Well, that has to do with the supremacy clause. So the supremacy clause is when a federal law is in conflict with the state's law.
The federal law, for example, in California, weed is legal, right?
Yes, but federally, federally, it's not. So they can come down here and they could say, hey, we're going to write all these places and they would be completely in line with.
And so this is how segregation and discrimination ended up existing, even after the civil rights laws of the 13th, 14th and 15th Amendment were passed, because Congress said we need to protect black people.
And the Supreme Court said we actually are not going to give you the right to do so.
For what it's worth, I think we can do this back and forth all day.
But at the end of the day, I will completely agree with you. Black people need to let the Democrats go.
I think black people need to let both of these parties go and figure out a way to move forward together in our own nation.
You know what? I can actually get on with that because, you know, I don't believe that all Republicans are, you know, good and not using us as well.
I agree with that. I agree with that.
Let's sing a duet.
I'm for I'm for no matter what color skin you are or black, whatever it is, think for yourself.